Alec Bravo

4705 Barbarossa Dr. San Diego CA. 92115 Cell 209-535-4710 | phsabravo@gmail.com | www.linkedin.com/in/alecbravo/

Summary

Data Analyst with 2 years experience eager to be part of an amazing team and ready to continue learning. Sourcing, organizing, and presenting data for outreach in an organized manner using various platforms is my specialty. Automating processes and creating workflows allow for increased productivity and the design of new business methods. I am highly passionate about data, environmental conservation, and opportunities to make a difference in a team-oriented environment.

Education

San Diego State University - Management Information Systems Major	2015 - 2019
San Diego Community College District	2015 - 2015
California State University of Stanislaus	2013 - 2014

Work Experience

Xponential Growth Solutions – Data Analyst and Research Assistant

May 2019 – June 2021

- Database Management Microsoft SQL Server
- Reporting Provide data to team in varied formats
- Data Mining Sourcing new contact data for outreach
- CRM Database Update and maintain Infusionsoft CRM
- Automation Automate daily processes for increased productivity

GoSite – Sales Development Representative

January 2019 – May 2019

- Learning about general business acumen, SaaS technology and sales psychology
- Responsible for outreach calls to businesses to introduce GoSite and exploring how our software can help their business thrive

Affiliated Organizations

Alpha Kappa Psi – Professional Co-ed Business Fraternity

- Appointed the Director of Technology
- Responsible for creating the fraternity website for student and business outreach
- Experienced a personal and professional developmental nine-week process, challenging my skills such as public speaking, organizational research, team leading, presentation leading, critical thinking, ability to have innovative ideas, communication, and time-management

AITP - Association of Information Technology Professionals

• Grows CS, IS, and CE student professionals with networking opportunities and knowledge of the field

Software

- SQL 1 ½ Year
- Infusionsoft
- Tableau
- MS Project

- Airtable
- Zapier
- Zoom
- Excel
- MS Access

- G Suite
- GoToWebinar
- Teamviewer
- Python (IntelliJ IDEA)

Skills

- Leadership
- Self-Starter
- Very Adaptable
- High Energy
- Collaboration
- Exceptional Soft Skills
- Project Management

- Bilingual-Spanish/ English
- Database Management
- Data Visualization
- Automation
- Data Cleaning
- Data Mining

- Outsourcing
- Web-Scraping
- Remote Work



Scan for LinkedIn